She's here. Anne. Huh? What?
To Jonas.
Show us what happened.
Why did you
show up here out of nowhere?
I was worried, so I just wanted
to make sure you were safe.
And. Good thing I did.
From now on,
I'll be around
to look after you.
Thanks, but that's
not too comforting coming
from someone who just
got attacked by thieves.
I'm confused though. You left
first. So how did I get ahead?
I'm guessing it was
because of that.
Quick stop.
I made him Reddington.
Hey. I feel like you're
not listening. Reddington.
Ah. That's where you
bought your warrior fairy.
It's handsome. Are you sure you
didn't buy a companion fairy?
Listen, Jonas, I'd really
prefer it if you went home.
This journey will be much
too dangerous for you.
I'm not going back. I'll
be escorting you to Lewiston.
Surely you know why? Because
I'm madly in love with you.
Well, uh. I hate to say it.
While I appreciate
your concern for me,
I can't help but worry
that you're confused.
I know you think you're in love,
No, I came here because I care.
Do you hate me?
Aren't you glad to see me?
Scarecrow.
We need to leave this place now.
The wild crows. They're
following the scent of blood.
Now that they've appeared,
the wolves won't be far behind.
Oh, no. Let's get out of here.
You have a man
to come and save you.
I thought you were just a child.
Well, I'm not a child.
I am 15 years of age.
I am an adult,
and he and I do not have
that sort of relationship.
Jonas feels sorry for me.
That is all. Is that it?
Either way, Jonas, it's time
for you to turn around.
You're not the kind
of person who should be
in a dangerous
situation like this.
Listen, Shaul,
since he's still behind us,
if anything happens, will you go
back there and help him out?
Please say it as an order
and I will
threaten to crush my wing
again with this.
Give me an order stuff.
Even though
you know what I mean.
What is that?
Barring an order from you,
I plan to do nothing.
I know that I purchased you
to serve me and everything,
but I told you
that makes me uncomfortable.
So I'm sticking with requests.
But if
you force me to order you,
I guess I have
no choice but to do so.
And I'll even say the whole bit
about ripping up your wing
if you don't do as I tell you.
But I'll always
try asking first.
You're the strangest scarecrow I've ever
met. Don't call me that.
No use, is it? So this is a fort
shelter. I've never been to one.
It's your first time.
What did you
do for shelter last night? Easy.
I just didn't stop. My goal was
to catch up to you
as quickly as I could.
Listen, tomorrow morning
you really should go.
So, you know, I happened to run
into you on a trip
for my own purposes.
So it's not as
though I'm following you.
Huh? What a headache.
Don't touch me.
You may possess my other wing,
but it's nothing more.
It's me.
Could you open the door, please?
Jonas?
Do you need something, miss? Oh,
Kathy, I didn't realize you
were here. I am Master.
Jonas Labor fairy,
so, of course, I.
Suppose I should have assumed
you would be. Now where's Jonas?
He's retired for the night,
I'm afraid.
Oh, that's all right.
Will you please
tell him to eat this soup
when he wakes up tomorrow?
Uh,
I could never expect him to eat
a single mouthful of something
so cruelly prepared.
I understand that if
he were at home.
is something to be grateful for.
It reeks of beast fat. Even
a fairy like me wouldn't eat it.
Oh, well, then,
excuse me for trying
to take care of everybody here.
What's that?
Is it food? Apparently not.
But this is your portion.
I'm sorry that my cooking
is so terrible.
This soup that smells like beast
fat. Not fitting for you either.
Now, what's the problem?
You act as
though your head is on fire.
Well, all Scarecrow's
heads are made out
of straw,
so that would make sense.
It's quite the blaze.
How can you blame me?
Smug little fairy told
me that a commoner
soup isn't good enough for the
heir to a sugar confectionery.
Might as well throw it out. Do
you find it disgusting as well?
No, I didn't say that.
It's just. I'm surprised.
Surprised by what?
Oh. It smells. It was
the fact that you handed a bowl
of soup to me
before serving yourself.
I don't understand when
you make food.
I'm pretty sure
having other people eat
first is the normal thing to do.
Oh, spoon.
I'm so sorry. I forgot it.
It just disappeared.
I'm done. You waited.
But how? We fairies don't
eat with our mouths.
We can absorb our food
by placing our hands over it.
I never knew it worked that way.
Well, did you enjoy it?
We don't taste it, so I couldn't
speak to the flavor.
Huh? Then again,
there's one thing we do taste.
What's that?
Silver sugar. It's sweet. Huh?
You like sugar confections?
I don't hate them.
I'll make some for you.
This might be hard to believe,
but I'm a bit
of a sugar artisan.
Is that so?
Oh. You bet. In fact,
when my mother was alive,
she was a silver sugar master.
Isn't that amazing? Most children grow
up playing around with clay,
but I have been toying
with Silver
sugar since before I figured
out how to walk.
I think something in a moon
flower shape would suit you.
So there's something in there.
Will you go.
Look? Order me too.
If I don't do it,
will you just tear up my wing?
That's not the point.
You can do it yourself then.
Fine.
I'll go see what's in there.
Is anyone here? Hey, human!
You best let go of me at once,
you lowlife! I'm warning you!
Are you punishing me?
That hurt! Stop being so rough.
I'm delicate, you know.
Would it kill you to be more
gentle with me?
You talk too much.
So you were the one
causing that ruckus?
How rude.
I wasn't causing any ruckus.
I had a nightmare, so I woke
up suddenly. That's all.
It must have been
a bad one then.
But that aside,
who are you? When
did you climb into my cart?
And what were you after?
I am the fairy
called Mithra Lipod.
And I've come to repay you.
To repay me?
Huh? What, you want me to say
thanks to a human, I refuse.
Are you the one from before?
Do you honestly not remember me?
It sure takes
a heartless person to
rescue someone
and then forget them.
What do you mean? If I rescued.
You, then how am I heartless?
Besides,
you were all covered in mud
last time. Well, the.
Important thing is that you
saved my life yesterday.
And I had to fulfill my duties.
So I hopped in the car.
But I seem to remember
you running away,
shouting about how you'd never
thank a human for anything.
Of course, that's because
I despise you humans.
But I had to do something,
you know?
Look, thanking you
and repaying you are
two very different things.
So tell me.
What you want. All right,
let me see here.
Oh, I know, could you oil
up the axles on the wagon?
Condescend me. You saved
my life. And you expect
me to repay you
with something that mundane?
Think of a more
impressive favor. What do you.
Mean by impressive favor? I don't know,
you figure it out and.
Get back to me. Ah, this fussy
little thing should be strangled.
If you order me to,
then I'll do it.
Wait. What did you say?
You can't do that.
Then I'll have saved
him for no reason.
Give me some time to think.
Mithra. Was it? It's Mithra.
Lynnport, don't shorten it. Ah!
All right. Mithra.
Lid pod. There is no reason
to repay me for what I did. I
saved you because it was right.
Not because I was hoping
to get anything in return.
You're free now, so you
should go live a happy life.
Listen to me, human girl.
My name's an er. Er.
Whoever you are,
you're clearly pretending to
be kind so that I'll leave.
But I'm going to repay you
the favor if it kills me.
Even if I have to follow you
down to the lowest depths
of the underworld.
That's ridiculous. We should
strangle him. Unhand me!
You dare!
Suddenly I am exhausted.
You a fairy tale? Let's go with
me, fairy killer. I'm sorry.
I'll make your sugar
confection tomorrow. Don't
try to steal your wing
while I'm a student.
Even if I don't try to.
Good luck sleeping.
Hey, what's the matter with you?
Don't
sleep at a time like this.
Wake up!
On.
There's still time
to throw him out.
Please don't do that.
It would be too cruel.
And besides, even if we did,
he'd just find us again.
After all, he did make it clear
that he would follow us
to the underworld.
Mama until we reach Lewiston
safely. Please watch over us.
Anne. Please understand. I'm just worried
about you, that's all.
I want to help you out. An.
300 Karen on the bloody highway.
So at this point,
turning around would be
even more dangerous.
You might as well
come to Lewiston
with us too.
Then you do understand?
I guess so, as long as you
understand how reckless
you're being. Certainly.
I think it's time I introduced
all of you properly.
This warrior fairy
is my friend Sheldon.
Shel, you haven't given
him a name yet.
I just told you his name,
didn't I?
But I like to call
him Shel for short.
Most people give their fairies
a human name, though.
You there?
You're so good looking. It seems
like a waste that you're
a warrior fairy.
You could be sold
as a companion type.
If you fancy me,
then buy me from the scarecrow.
I'd still be working
for an idiot.
Either way,
it makes no difference which
one of you is my master.
I'm an idiot.
That's rude.
Sorry, Jonas. Ciao is a
little bit of a sharp tongue.
He's called me
a hurtful name more
times than I can count already.
Please don't take it personally.
Uh, right.
You don't need to apologize.
And by the way,
what about that one?
You mean me? You may address
me as Lord Mithra. Lid pod.
He better not
forget the Lord part.
Lord, it's all right.
Ah, you're every bit
as arrogant as Shel is,
aren't you?
It's one thing if you
behave that way with me.
But leave everyone
else out of it,
you hear me?
Now it's time to eat.
I guess with a delicious
meal like that,
I suppose you have
no desire for my soup then?
Of course not.
I told you it reeks.
I could smell the beast
fat from over here.
Silence, Cathy,
keep your opinions to yourself.
I forbid you to speak
to Anne so rudely.
Oh, I apologize, Master Jonas.
I was only trying to disappear.
I'm sorry. Anne, my labor fairy
still needs a little training.
Your soup was truly delicious.
I can't wait to have it again.
Oh, um. Thank you. The way Jonas
treats his fairy
is probably the correct
way to behave as her master.
But still.
So your fairy
can erase her form.
That's impressive, though it does pale in
comparison to my own ability.
What kind of powers
do you possess? Mithril.
It's not that surprising.
In the northernmost
part of the Kingdom of Highland,
there lies a great body
of water known as Lois Lake.
One day,
a drop of water fell on a leaf.
And that's how I was born.
That's interesting.
Does that mean all fairies
are born from drops of water?
Wow, you're completely clueless,
aren't you? Fairies
are born
from all sorts of things.
Grass, seeds,
fruit and nuts from trees.
Basically, it's when a lot
of energy pulls up in something.
For that to happen,
the object must be gazed
upon by a living being,
human or animal.
It doesn't matter.
That causes the energy
to take form and poof,
a brand new fairy appears.
Ah, so tell us what
you were born from.
Based on his looks,
I'd say obsidian
fairies who were created
from precious stones
have the ability
to create sharp objects.
And because I came
from a water drop,
I can control water.
It's kind of my specialty.
Control water? That's amazing.
Can I see?
Sure thing. Ready? Ta da! Huh?
It's cold. That's
very impressive. So what can
you use your power for, huh?
I just showed you.
Oh, is that all? What do.
You mean? Is that all? How dare
you be so underwhelmed
at the great wonder that is me?
Throw lit pot.
I suppose it would be useful
in giving water to tiny birds.
Die. No one asked you.
And what kind
of comment is that?
You better not
be making fun of me
bad, huh? What's the problem?
Oh.
Uh oh, you weren't kidding.
That is bad.
I don't get it. What's
the matter, Anne? Look above.
They going to attack us?
Wild crows are scavengers
that search for carcasses.
But when they can't
find anything that's dead,
they form a massive flock
and kiss something.
They had a small taste of bandit
blood two days ago,
and now they want more.
Can you stop them?
I'm giving you an order.
Shell do whatever you must
to save us from those birds.
Don't forget that I have your
other wing. Obey or be sorry.
Stop the car.
Go hide in the cargo hold.
Get in. You should get
inside too quickly.
Now's my chance to repay the favor.
I'll chase those crows away.
So you two.
I save a shell?
Don't be scared, Anne.
We'll be fine.
Shell thin shell isn't
like us. He's made of obsidian.
He won't get hurt.
He won't break.
It's over.
Huh?
You won.
Did your legs give out? Of
course not. That's silly. Huh?
My scarecrow. I'm shocked.
This is what you want from me?
Huh? No, I would never.
I thank you for protecting me,
shell. That's all I needed.
This is bad. We can't
keep getting sidetracked.
What's wrong? Ann?
At this rate, we can't
reach the fort
shelter by sunset.
Those crows really threw a wrench in
our schedule. Oh, but wait.
A doctor's in. Sorry.
What's a doctor's in?
Exactly what it sounds like.
It's an inn
where doctors allow
people to take refuge,
and doctors rarely
get attacked by bandits.
It's not a fort shelter, but it's
the safest alternative there is.
That's quite an old map, though.
Are
you sure we can rely on it?
Well, mama drew this map
so it won't lead us astray.
That's where we'll be staying
tonight. Now let's go.
Please let us make it a time.
It's possible, right? I'm
certain mama could have done it.
This mother of yours.
Where is she?
Two weeks back.
And I swore I would become a
silver sugar master
just like her.
I'm competing in a contest
in Lewiston,
and if the King really
likes my work there,
then I can actually become one.
I have to. And this year,
you know, why don't you?
The pulse. All day is in winter.
It's a formal send
off to the heavens
for people who died that year.
There's a silver sugar master.
I can make
the most amazing sugar
confections there's ever been.
So that way mama sees it
before she leaves this world.
Then she will know not to worry.
And then she can go in peace.
A good idea. Shall.
So that's why. A light.
Wild crows. That's quite the calamity.
Well, at least you're safe.
This room's for
you and your fairy.
Your friend is next door.
Once you've
settled in and rested up,
come to the dining hall.
We should be able
to serve you all.
A simple meal, perhaps a soup.
A real bad. I missed this and.
You must be hungry.
Let's take them
up on that food offer.
It's fine.
I'll just lie here for a while.
You don't have to be so polite.
I'm sure you're starving
after today's journey, right?